<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Thrumbo Race</name>
  <author>Naharri, Cenbes</author>
  <url>https://github.com/Cenbes/Ginger-Thrumbo</url>
  <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
			<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
  <description>This mod about a Thrumbo / Thrumboian race.  
  
  REQUIRES ALIEN FRAMEWORK to be loaded BEFORE / ABOVE this mod. 

  
  Perks of the Thrumboian:
 - Half the health of a Thrumbo (4.0x for this Race vs 8.0x Thrumbo base)
 - Innate armor double that of a Thrumbo, to make up for the lack of health:
	80% blunt, 120% sharp, and 60% heat.
 - Thrumbo Horn!  Not as powerful as a Thrumbo... but hey still a weapon.
 - They live as long as a Thrumbo, 220 years.
 - Clothing optional for the most part along with a few other perks:
	They have the same weather needs as a Thrumbo -65C to 50C
	Don't care about nudity, sleeping outside, sleeping on the floor, eating raw foods, butchering stuff, tables or observing corpses
 - A Rage when injured and bleeding, giving them an slight edge when fighting.
 - They are 10% faster at... well everything.
 - They tend wounds 25% better than most humans!
 - Cannot get: badback, frail, cataracts, hearing loss, dementia, alzheimers, or asthma.
 - Also cannot have the traits: Jealous, Greedy, Cannibal, Chemical fascination, Chemical interest, AnnoyingVoice, CreepyBreathing, Pyromaniac, or Wimp.
 - Innately more resistant to toxins.
 - Move slightly slower than an angry Thrumbo, but faster than most pawns.
 - Lastly, they can carry more than others, by nearly double, making them excellent caravaners.
 
 Neutral:
 - Vegetarian animal diet, meaning only Meals, Kibble, Hay, and other greenery, like Grass. 

 Disadvantages of the Thrumboian:
 - Unlike the Thrumbo, a Thrumboian cannot eat trees as they are too small.
 - Are worth a lot, adding to colony value making raids harder just by being there.
 - Only available via Raids from a hidden faction, Thrumbo Scenario, or the Mod Prepare Carefully.
 - Raids by the Thrumboian Race will be... tough, so be prepared.
 - Hunting Stealth is very poor, meaning much more likely to cause animal revenge when hunting.
 - Hard to kill when attacking and harder to keep down.
 - Also very hard to recruit.
 - While they have a Thrumbo Horn, they do NOT drop it when butchered.
 - BUT their leather is Thrumbo Fur.
 
 The Thrumboians have only 1 extra part:
 - A Thrumbo Horn, replaceable with Steel and Plasteel Horn which includes its own graphics.
 
 
 However, other than a Horn replacements, there are NO changes to their base form, which SHOULD make them compatible with any mod that alters their bodies.  Such as EPOE or the like.
 
 Known issues:
 - Decaying Thrumboians do NOT have a horn, but their skeletons do.  At this time I cannot figure out how to change this. 
 
 
Change Log:
1.0.1 -added a graphic and graphic path for the Thrumbo Race Hidden Villages.
1.0.2 -changed starting research level to allow for Thrumbo starting scenario to be able to research.
1.0.3 -altered stats to actually give 70Kg caravan carry capacity vs vanilla 35.
1.0.4 -changed starting research tech to Tribal. 
1.0.5 -edited some values to be more in line with where they were supposed to be and less overpowered.  Like hauling capacity, hunting stealth, and horn attack chance. 
1.1.0 -Added plasteel horn, tweaked values to reasemble more their animal spirit, tweaked allowed thougts, fixed soaking wet thought. All changed can be found in root mod folder in README_UPDATE.
Mod now supports 1.0 and 1.1
 
 
 
 
 
 
 This race was primarily made for my spouse and myself, mostly because we wanted an race that had a lot of perks and few downsides, and as of the making of this no one else made a Thrumbo race.  This mod was made for our enjoyment of the game, but figured others might enjoy it so I am posting it.  
 
 
 I would like to state my thanks for everyone who supports Rimworld, both Tynan Sylvester and all the modders out there.  Seriously this is a great community and this game is one of the best I have ever had the pleasure to experience, both the original work and of course mods!



 This mod was cobbled together by myself and what little art has been a combined effort of my spouse and I. 
 
 
  </description>
</ModMetaData>